sourcecodeonline.com 2011-12-31

# Source Code Online Privacy Policy Information

Our Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for sourcecodeonline.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of this site. 

## 1\. Types of information collected and use of information

Please note that we at sourcecodeonline.com collect two types of user information: a) non-personally identifiable information and b) private data from our users or visitors. 

a) Non-personally identifiable information includes technical information, such as Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and/or your Internet Protocol ("IP") address as well as search engine and keywords use. This information helps afterwards to analyze how visitors find our site, what technologies are used to access it and which pages interest them all. Having aggregated this data allows us to create new mechanisms for bringing our site on top ranks during Internet search thus providing our visitors with the most efficient and smooth service. 

Other technical data include changes in trends, such as screen resolution, operating system, etc. This information is taken into account while planning the website design usability and accessibility. The complete set of technical data helps us to offer our visitors an outstanding service and customize the website according to visitors' interests and search engine optimization requirements. 

b) We do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent. However, the site provides the opportunity for our users to submit source codes and software products after having registered in our online form. sourcecodeonline.com is committed to our users' privacy, personal data protection and security. Therefore no personal data will be ever made available, sold or bartered to the third-parties. We may use this data for site purposes only (such as mailing lists generation, site updates notifications or software resources promotion) or under condition of special service requests. 

## 2\. Release of information

Neither of the types of user data collected at our site will be released to third parties or made publicly available. However, under certain circumstances we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

## 3\. How we use cookies

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us to analyze web page traffic data and to monitor which pages you find useful and which do not. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Our site also contains ads from external companies. These advertisers will also generally store cookies on a visitor's computer to record tracking information such as which ad the visitor followed to reach the advertiser's website, date visited, etc. The advertiser will usually delete the cookies automatically after a certain expiration period (depends on the advertiser). In order to compile with modern trends we use Google Adsense to support our site. Ads displayed by Google AdSense are targeted to be relevant to the content of the website and / or page they are on (i.e. the information is collected from the website contents only, not from visitors themselves). Google Adsense also uses cookies to publish ads on our site. Google's use of DART cookies enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

## 4\. Disclaimer

Providing free opportunities to submit source codes or software products, we at sourcecodeonline.com are not responsible for the contents of the information published. If you believe that the information is incorrect, faulty, abusive, etc. please contact a person or an organization which has submitted the corresponding data. Our site provides sufficient contact data of a person or an organization making a posting in our website categories. 

## 5\. Links to other web sites

As stated above, all the information about our users and visitors (both personally and non-personally identifiable information) is kept secure and protected. However, our site can offer you links to other sites. Please be aware that as soon as you leave sourcecodeonline.com we do not have control over privacy policies of these other sites. Therefore, before using other sites resources or disclosing any personal information we do encourage you to exercise caution and look at the privacy policies of other sites to make sure that your personal information is treated appropriately. 

## 6\. Contact us

In case of any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, you can [contact us](http://www.sourcecodeonline.com/contact.html)
